[{"id": 1183, "question": "Nowadays everybody seems to think that they know English. Many people speak it but few speak it really well. Practice is necessary in speaking English well. Reading is also one of the things that will help you to speak English better. Read whenever you can and whatever you like! Read papers and Internet sites that you like in English every day. Then, you will see that the number of known words is increasing and you are able to speak with more skills. Then you will have made the foundations and a good basis of English. It is not good to stop and get stuck there. Going to England or an English speaking country is a good choice, but many people cannot afford it. If you cannot go, reading and speaking with your friends will also help you to practice your English. However, I think that it is ve...\n\nQ: According to the passage, what may make the author excited?", "options": ["Reading papers and Internet sites.", "Having a good basis of English.", "Going to an English speaking country.", "A native speaker's praise."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3387, "question": "Life is too short to waste a moment, so while you still have time, let your hair down, remove that \"boring\" tag in your so-called life and start making it worthwhile. Below are some tips that will help you live a wonderful life. 1. Keep a Positive Attitude. Enjoy what you have and work on getting the things you desire. Psychologists believe that optimism is a good defense against unhappiness, so it is better to keep your optimism alive. Feeling sad about your life will only make you sadder, so be happy. 2. Don't Be Afraid to Take Risks. Life is all about taking risks, and that's the exciting part of it. Challenges and failure are part of life. Once you learn how to take risks, you'll soon realize how good it feels not to let moments pass you by. 3. You only have one life, so make it worthw...\n\nQ: What is the writer's attitude toward life?", "options": ["Positive.", "Negative.", "Doubtful.", "Indifferent."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 129, "question": "Three Central Texas men were honored with the Texas Department of Public Safety's Director's Award in a Tuesday morning ceremony for their heroism in saving the victims of a fiery two car accident. The accident occurred on March 25 when a vehicle lost control while traveling on a rain-soaked State Highway 6 near Baylor Camp Road. It ran into an oncoming vehicle, leaving the occupants trapped inside as both vehicles burst into flames. Bonge was the first on the scene and heard children screaming. He broke through a back window and pulled Mallory Smith, 10, and her sister, Megan Smith,9,from the wreckage. The girls' mother, Beckie Smith, was not with them at the time of the wreck, as they were traveling with their baby sitter, Lisa Bow bin. Beckie Smith still remembers the sickening feeling ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage?", "options": ["Luckily, no one received too serious injuries in the accident.", "All the victims received slight injuries in the accident.", "The rescuers were taken to the hospital to visit the victims.", "The injured will soon recover from their injuries."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1709, "question": "Everyone, please think of your biggest personal goal. For real - you can take a second. You've got to feel this to learn it. Take a few seconds and think of your personal biggest goal, okay? Imagine deciding right now that you're going to do it. Imagine telling someone that you meet today what you're going to do. Imagine their congratulations and their high image of you. Doesn't it feel good to say it out loud? Don't you feel one step closer already, like it's already becoming part of your identity? Well, bad news: you should have kept your mouth shut, because that good feeling now will make you less likely to do it. Repeated psychology tests have proved that telling someone your goal makes it less likely to happen. Any time you have a goal, there are some steps that need to be done, some ...\n\nQ: What did Peter Gollwitzer find in his tests?", "options": ["Writing down personal goals inspired people to work hard to achieve them.", "Those who didn't tell others their goals were more likely to achieve them.", "Those who kept working hard tended to feel that they were closer to realizing their goals.", "Those who made their goals public worked harder than those who kept them secret."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 614, "question": "Educating Girls Is a Real Lifesaver Clare Short knows it. Every developing economist knows it. The World Bank knows it. The education of girls is the surest way to reduce poverty. The reason is simple. All the evidence shows that taking girls out of the fields and homes, and putting them behind desks, raises economic productivity, lowers infant and maternal death rates, reduces birth rates, and improves environmental management. Why, then, are 90 million primary school-age girls around the world not in school? For the same reason that when Charles Dickens was writing David Copperfield 150 years ago girls were absent from the British education system: Men in power mostly prefer _ that way, or are not interested enough in changing the situation to commit energy and money to doing so. The cou...\n\nQ: What does the author think of girls' education?", "options": ["essential", "terrible", "indifferent", "helpless"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1068, "question": "The Opening of the Book Nook Saturday, October 4, 10 AM to 10 PM You will not want to miss the opening of your new neighborhood bookstore! Located at 2289 Main Street, the Book Nook is within walking distance of schools, many homes and businesses. Come and check out the Book Nook on Saturday! Activities will include: * Live music by local musicians * One Book-of-the-Month Club membership giveaway Wide Selection The Book Nook has three floors with books of all kinds---any kind you could want. If we do not have the book you are looking for, we can specially order it for you. You will have it in your hands within two days! Reading Nooks We are proud of our children's reading area on the first floor, as well as our teenagers' nook on the second floor. Come for the activities and stay for a whi...\n\nQ: What can people do in the Book Nook on October 4?", "options": ["They can have a taste of different kinds of chocolate.", "They can read aloud together with well-known writers.", "They can enjoy live music performed by well-known writers.", "They can become a member of the Book-of-the-Month Club."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1544, "question": "About ten years ago, a young and very successful businessman named Josh was traveling down a Chicago neighborhood street. He was going a bit too fast in his shiny, black, 12 cylinder Jaguar XKE, which was only two months old. He was watching for kids rushing out from between parked cars and slowed down when he thought he saw something. As his car passed, no child came out, but a brick sailed out and - WHUMP! - it hit the Jaguar's shiny black side door! SCREECH ... ! ! ! ! Immediately Josh stopped the car, jumped out, seized the kid and pushed him up against a parked car. He shouted at the kid, \"What was that all about and who are you? Just what the heck are you doing?!\" \"That's my new Jaguar, that brick you threw is gonna cost you a lot of money. Why did you throw it?\" \"Please, mister, ple...\n\nQ: The boy threw a brick at the businessman's car because   _  .", "options": ["he wanted to ask for some money", "he wanted to get help from the driver", "the businessman drove at a high speed", "he hated the brand-new car very much"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1385, "question": "Do you want to be a successful person? Would you like to know how successful people usually think and what drives them? Here I am going to tell you the key to success that successful people share. First of all, successful people never blame someone or something outside of themselves for their failure to move ahead. They realize that their future lies in their own hands. They understand that they can't control things in life, such as nature, the past and other people. At the same time, they are well aware that they can control their own thoughts and actions. They take responsibility for their life. Perhaps what most separates successful people from others is that they live life \"on purpose\" --- they are doing what they believe they are put here to do. In their opinion, having a purpose in t...\n\nQ: The author's purpose in writing this passage is to   _  .", "options": ["explain the exact meaning of success", "share the key to success with readers", "tell his experience of achieving success", "encourage readers to learn from failure"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 475, "question": "\"Show them the money!\" That's what some people are saying for college athletes. They say students who play sports for their school should receive salaries. Top athletes should be paid because many of them practice full time, Mark Jameson argues. Rico Cannon, a former college football player, agrees. \"Nonathletes can get a job for extra spending money, but many student athletes spend so many hours in training that they don't have time to work,\" he explains. \"Shouldn't athletes be able to earn extra money too?\" The students also make money for their schools when people buy tickets to their games. The players should receive some of that cash, supporter Robbie Pokora reasons. College athletes are about honor and tradition, but they're also a business. Thanks to ticket sales, there's money for ...\n\nQ: Who supports the idea of paying student athletes?", "options": ["Kaitlyn Rentala", "Robbie Pokora", "Michael Massett", "Kate Macrae"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3301, "question": "Street art can be found on buildings, sidewalks, street signs and even trash cans from Tokyo to Paris to New York City. This special kind of art can take the form of paintings, sculptures, cloth or even stickers. Street art has become part of a global visual culture. Now, even art museums and galleries are collecting the work of street artists. It is not easy to provide an exact history of the street art movement. This kind of art has developed in many kinds of ways in places all over the world. Also, because it is illegal to paint public and private property without permission, street artists usually work secretly. This secretive nature of street art and its countless forms make it hard to define exactly. And people have different opinions about the movement. Some think street art is a cr...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true according to the passage?", "options": ["TAG was a word created by people to distinguish street artists and the other artists.", "There are three reasons to explain why it is hard to define the history of street art.", "The movement of street art began in the 1980s in New York City.", "Not all the people think that the street art is a rich form of cultural expression."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2190, "question": "Recently a committee of the National Academy of Sciences inprefix = st1 /Washingtonreleased a report .It confirmed that world temperatures increased about six-tenths of a degree Celsius in the last one hundred years. The report also confirmed evidence that the level of carbon dioxide in increasing. The best information about climate in the past comes from tests of ice many kilometers deep in Antarctica and Greenland .These tests show that levels of carbon dioxide today are the highest ever measured .These findings have led scientists to believe that carbon dioxide is a major cause of climate warming. Carbon dioxide is released into the atmosphere when fuel is burned. Oil ,coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas .When biological waste breaks down ,it also releases carbon dioxide. H...\n\nQ: According to this passage ,those people disagree with the control of carbon dioxide because    .", "options": ["they think that carbon is beneficial for plant growth", "they want to use more fuels that can send out carbon dioxide", "they think it will destroy the natural balance of gases in the world", "they think carbon dioxide is not the main reason for global warming"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2024, "question": ". Passage 1 Every morning, when we wake up, we have 24 brand-new hours to live. What a gift! We have the capacity to live in a way that these 24 hours will bring peace, joy, and happiness to ourselves and to others. Peace is right here and now, in ourselves and in everything we do and see. The question is whether or not we are in touch with it. We don't have to travel far away to enjoy the blue sky. We don't have to leave our city or even our neighborhood to enjoy the eyes of a beautiful child. Even the air we breathe can be a source of joy. We can smile, breathe, walk, and eat our meals in a way that allows us to be in touch with the abundance of happiness that is available. We are very good at preparing how to live, but not very good at living. We know how to sacrifice ten years for a di...\n\nQ: Which of the following phrases from Passage 2would the author of Passage 1 most likely choose as a title for Passage 1?", "options": ["\"the hedonist and the guru\" (line 1)", "\"a brief breathing space\" (line 11)", "\"the feast before us\" (line 2)", "\"an unwelcome guest\" (line 14)"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2306, "question": "Engineers should embrace the arts, Sir John O'Reilly, a fellow of the Institution of Engineering and Technology, argued in a lecture. About 59% of engineering companies in the IET's 2014 survey feared skill shortages could threaten business. \"There is nothing as creative as engineering,\" Sir John told the reporter. He says science, technology, engineering and mathematics - often known as \"Stem\" subjects, are vital for a modern knowledge economy. But there is a massive shortfall in the number of recruits - with a recent study by the Royal Academy of Engineering saying the UK needs to increase by as much as 50% the number of Stem graduates it produces. Delivering this year's Mountbatten Lecture at the Royal Institution, Sir John argued that engineers should recognise the role of the arts in ...\n\nQ: According to the lecture Full Steam Ahead for Growth,   _   .", "options": ["engineers should cooperate with arts majors", "Accepting the arts could attract more people into engineering", "engineers should realize arts play the most important part in their work", "engineering and technology is as diverse and creative as before"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2714, "question": "The Sunset Pasta Cruise to Emerald Bay Saturday evening, September 25, 2010 You will cruise to Emerald Bay at Sunset, one of the most beautiful places in the world while dining on a Pasta Buffet and listening to live light dance music. Buses will pick up Sunset Pasta Cruise diners from the main entrance to the Horizon Casino Resort at: 4:40pm and 5:05pm on Saturday and take you the 1.5 miles to Ski Run Marina for boarding. Boarding is at Ski Run Marina at 5:15 p.m. (with departure at 5:45 p.m.), located in South Lake Tahoe. The cost for the cruise, pasta buffet, live music, and the 2.5-hour cruise to Emerald Bay is $55 (normally $75). The cost for children between 3-11 is $41 and under 3 is free. Must register the under 3 as well for the coast guard count. The Sunset Pasta Cruise will be l...\n\nQ: When will the cruise to Emerald Bay end?", "options": ["At about 7:00 pm.", "At about 8:20 pm.", "At about 9:20 pm.", "On Sunday morning."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 182, "question": "There are a growing number of pet owners who feed their pets on raw, which means, \"uncooked\" meat and bones. William Burk, a pet food specialist from the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), believes that feeding raw meat to pets is against its goal of protecting the public from health dangers, and that raw meat and bones do not have all the required nutrition that a pet needs every day. Recognizing how popular these foods are, the FDA has provided guidelines for producers of pet foods which contain uncooked meat for dogs, cats and other pets. The guidelines give rules to protect pet owners and pets from dangers about food safety and lack of nutrition. Pet owners who feed raw meat and bones to their pets should deal with these products very carefully to protect themselves against possible d...\n\nQ: The FDA has provided guidelines for producers of pet foods with raw meat because   _  .", "options": ["pet safety is a serious problem", "most pets are lack of nutrition", "feeding pets on raw is popular", "the quality of pet foods is dropping"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3134, "question": "For some reason, it takes constant reminders that weprimates need nurturing. In a recent study of 46 babychimpanzee orphans, Kim Bard of the University of Portsmouth in England and her colleagues demonstrated that primate babies that have tight relationships with mother figures do much better oncognitive tests than babies who receive only food, shelter, and friendship with peers. But this is not breaking mews. In fact, it's old news. In the 1950s, Harry Harlow conducted a series of experiments with baby monkeys that showed, without doubt, that lack of love and comfort makes for a crazy monkey. Harlow constructed a cage that included a wire monkey \"mother\" topped with a plastic face. In this wire he fixed Mom with a milk bottle. The cage also held another wire mother covered with terry clot...\n\nQ: The study Kim Bard and his colleagues did   _  .", "options": ["included 46 baby and mother monkeys", "was nothing new to people about the findings", "showed that many chimpanzees lacked love when they were young", "showed that many chimpanzees had good relationships with their mothers"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1653, "question": "Do you love Beats headphones, True Religion jeans, and UGG shoes? These are some of the most popular brands around. They are also expensive. But some experts say they are not much better than cheaper brands. For example, Jim Wilcox works for Consumer Reports. He tested all kinds of headphones. He says that $80 Koss Pro headphones provide basically the same quality and comfort as Beats. So why do people pay twice or even 10 times as much for the hottest brands? Experts say it's because fashionable, expensive brands send a message. Brands say \"I belong\" or \"I can afford it.\" Some people think that expensive brand names are worth the price. They say that some designer clothes really are top quality and that they last longer than cheaper brands. Some teenagers choose to wear popular brands bec...\n\nQ: Who have the same opinion on expensive brands?", "options": ["Alexandra & Daniel", "Emmy & Edmund.", "Emmy & Alexandra.", "Daniel & Emmy."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1132, "question": "We are not rich by what we possess but rather by what we can do without. ----Immauel Kant Many times my friend June would say, \"If I ever get rich, I'm getting a completely new wardrobe and moving into a bigger apartment.\" I thought of her words and her chances of being rich are about as good as mine. But, to everyone's surprise, a few years ago June did come to large inheritance . At first June said very little about the money. As the initial shock disappeared, she became excited, June is a great believer in making lists, so I was surprised to find her writing down all the ways she would spend her new wealth. As time went on, she started revising the list. What had been midway down the list was now at the top. At last, I said to her, \"You know, it isn't necessary to spend all your inherit...\n\nQ: When June called the writer to talk about her new decision, the writer  _  .", "options": ["felt that June would do something meaningful", "refused the invitation at first, but changed her mind later", "had decided not to make any comments on June's list", "was eager to learn more about the new list"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2933, "question": "Scientists estimate that more than 60 percent of cancer deaths in the United States are preventable through lifestyle changes. Although there is no certain way to avoid all cancers, reducing individual risk factors greatly decreases the likelihood of getting many forms of this dangerous disease. The American Chemical Society estimates that smoking causes nearly 30 percent of all cancer deaths in the United States -- that is, about 166,000 cancer deaths each year. All cancer deaths caused by tobacco smoking could be prevented completely by not smoking and not using smokeless tobacco. For those who already smoke, quitting will reduce the risk of developing cancer. Studies show that after about ten years of not smoking, a past smoker's risk lowers to about the level of those who have never sm...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the author?", "options": ["A person drinking tea regularly will not be likely to suffer from cancer.", "Once a smoker has stopped smoking, there is almost no chance for cancers.", "A balanced diet is absolutely effective in preventing one from getting cancer.", "Those having quitted smoking for 10 years and non-smokers have less cancer risk."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1069, "question": "The Opening of the Book Nook Saturday, October 4, 10 AM to 10 PM You will not want to miss the opening of your new neighborhood bookstore! Located at 2289 Main Street, the Book Nook is within walking distance of schools, many homes and businesses. Come and check out the Book Nook on Saturday! Activities will include: * Live music by local musicians * One Book-of-the-Month Club membership giveaway Wide Selection The Book Nook has three floors with books of all kinds---any kind you could want. If we do not have the book you are looking for, we can specially order it for you. You will have it in your hands within two days! Reading Nooks We are proud of our children's reading area on the first floor, as well as our teenagers' nook on the second floor. Come for the activities and stay for a whi...\n\nQ: As a member of the Book-of-the-Month Club, you   _  .", "options": ["can buy any books in the Book Nook at a low price", "may borrow as many as 12 books every week", "need to pay 120 dollars every year", "should be over the age of 12"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3070, "question": "Ladji Doucoure of France beat Olympic champion Liu Xiang of China in the final meters to claim the title of the men's 110 meters hurdles at the 10thworld championships in Helsinki on Friday. Doucoure, who led the world this season with 12.97 seconds, over took the Chinese to win the race in 13.07 seconds. Liu was second in 13.08. Four-time world champion Allen Johnson of the United States took the third in 13.10. The 22-year-old Doucoure said after the race, \" I can not tell you just how long I have been dreaming of this. This victory is the result of a lot of hard work, and also a lot of support from people who have believed in me. I had a bad start, touched a few hurdles, but after the 4thhurdle I _ and went straight to the finish line.\" Liu, who won the Olympic gold with a world record-...\n\nQ: The following statements about Doucoure are true EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["He won the gold medal in the men's 110m hurdles in Helsinki.", "He led the world in the men's 110m hurdles with 12.97 seconds this season.", "He did a lot of hard practice before the race in Helsinki.", "He won the world champion title four times."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1235, "question": "Joan, super visor of the town's morals recently accused George, a local man, of having a drinking problem because she noticed his car outside the town's only bar.She reasoned, it was a logical assumption .George stared at her for a moment and said nothing.Later that evening, he parked his car in front of her house and left it there all night. Why is it that so many of our logical assumptions are just plain wrong? And why do we want to act as if they must be true? In an age long before the Internet, a young American at a party found himself seated next to the famous Chinese diplomat Wellington Koo.Completely not knowing what to say to someone from such a different culture, this young man turned and asked, \"Likee soupee?\" After all, he assumed, don't all Chinese speak in broken English? Mr.K...\n\nQ: Red roses are so popular at the market in that   _  .", "options": ["women prefer red roses.", "women like the red color1 best.", "they smell pleasant than others.", "men think women would like them."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1468, "question": "New rules and behavior standards for the middle school students came out in March. Middle school is going to use a new way to decide who the top students are. The best students won't only have high marks. They will also be kids who don't dye their hair, smoke or drink. The following are some of the new rules. Tell the truth. Have you ever copied others' work in an exam? Don't do it again if you did it before! That's not something an honest student should do. If you have played computer games for two hours in your room, don't tell your parents you have done your homework. Do more at school. Good students love animals and care for other people. April is a bird-loving month in China. Did your school do anything to celebrate? If so, you should join it! In this way, you can learn more about ani...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is NOT true?", "options": ["Protect yourself when you are out.", "Tell the truth, even when you are wrong.", "Keep some animals to protect them.", "Use the Internet, but keep away from bad things."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2536, "question": "When you sleep somewhere else--like at summer camp or a friend's house--you know you're in for a fun time. It can be exciting to get away from the same old bed in the same old room in the same old house. But fun as this is, for some kids being away from home can be scary and sad. They want to go and have fun with their friends, but once they're there, they start to miss their good old bed, their good old parents, and all that everyday stuff at home. It's called being homesick. Homesick means you're upset, sad, and maybe scared. But don't feel surprised. A lot of people get homesick, even grownups. When you're used to having certain people and things around you, it can be scary when they're gone. When you're dealing with other problems, you will feel homesick, too. Some kids may feel more h...\n\nQ: _   is NOT TRUE according to the passage.", "options": ["Kids can keep touching with their family with telephone", "You can tell friends you are feeling homesick", "Bringing some familiar things with you can help to feel less homesick", "Only kids get homesick, grownups never feel homesick"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1425, "question": "If women are mercilessly exploited year after year, they have only themselves to blame. Because they tremble at the thought of being seen in public in clothes that are out of fashion, they are always taken advantage of by the designers and the big stores. Clothes which have been worn only a few times have to be put aside because of the change of fashion. When you come to think of it, only a woman is capable of standing in front of a wardrobe packed full of clothes and announcing sadly that she has nothing to wear. Changing fashions are nothing more than the intentional creation of waste. Many women spend vast sums of money each year to replace clothes that have hardly been worn. Women who cannot afford to throw away clothing in this way, waste hours of their time altering the dresses they ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["Fashion designs should not be encouraged since they are only welcomed by women.", "The constant changes in women's clothing reflect their strength of character.", "The fashion industry makes an important contribution to society.", "New fashions in clothing are created for the commercial exploitation of women."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2031, "question": "Is your family interested in buying a dog? A dog can be a pleasant companion to your family, but if you choose the wrong kind of dog , you will have a lot of troubles. Families should sit down and discuss the possible problems before buying a dog. Even if the children in your family are the ones who want the dog, the parents are the ones who are really responsible for seeing that the animal is properly cared for. If you don't know much about dogs, it is a good idea to go to the library for books about different kinds of dogs, and books about how to train a young dog. In reading about the different breeds you should know that a dog described as very alert may be too active. When a book describes a dog as an excellent hunting dog, it probably means that the dog won't be happy living in a sma...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is not true?", "options": ["Don't buy a hunting dog if your house is not big enough.", "A dog may not be so good as it is described in books.", "The German shepherd never loses its popularity for it provides not only companionship but also protection.", "You should have a discussion with your family before buying a dog in case it causes you a lot of troubles."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2814, "question": "Trees are useful to man in three very important ways: they provide him with wood and other products, they give him shade, and they help to prevent drought and floods. Unfortunately, in many parts of the world man has not realized that the third of these services is the most important. In his eagerness to draw quick profit from the trees, he has cut them down in large numbers, only to find that without them he has lost the best friends he had. Two thousand years ago a rich and powerful country cut down its trees to build warships, with which to gain itself an empire. It gained the empire but, without its trees, its soil became hard and poor. When the empire fell to pieces, the country found itself faced by floods and starvation. Even though a government realizes the importance of a plentifu...\n\nQ: According to the article we know it is    _    to prevent the forests from slowly disappearing.", "options": ["necessary but impossible", "necessary but difficult", "impossible and unimportant", "difficult and impossible"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3377, "question": "New rules for pubs and clubs, including a ban on drinking games like the awful \"dentist's chair\", will be introduced in Britain this year to prevent the heavy drinking culture, which costs the country billions of pounds a year. Other activities like \"all you can drink for 10 pounds \", \"women drink free\" nights and speed drinking competitions will also be banned. But, on the other hand, offers of cheap alcohol in supermarkets will not be affected, which is widely regarded as one of the main sources of Britain's problems with under-age and over-drinking. Doctors and health experts argue that the government has failed to use its most effective weapon, the taxation of minimum price controls on alcohol. Home Secretary Alan Johnson said that the government and the industry had a duty to act on h...\n\nQ: Some people believe when the tough new rules come into effect,   _  .", "options": ["supermarkets will stop selling alcohol in low prices", "\"women drink free\" nights will not be closed", "over-drinking will still not be stopped", "under-age people will not continue drinking"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2976, "question": "Most Americans receive at least two or three credit card applications in the mail every month.Why have credit cards become so popular? For a merchant, the answer is obvious.By putting charge slips in a bank, the merchant can change credit card sales into cash.In return for processing the merchant's credit card transactions , the bank charges a fee that ranges between 1.5 and 5 percent. The easiest way to establish credit is to open checking and savings accounts at your local bank.Then apply for a gasoline or store credit card.These cards are fairly easy to get because retailers want you to buy their goods and services.The third step, and the most dangerous one, is obtaining a major credit card like Visa, MasterCard, or American Express. It is important to choose a credit card carefully bec...\n\nQ: What is the author's attitude towards credit cards?.", "options": ["Critical.", "Pessimistic.", "Neutral.", "Optimistic"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2383, "question": "I was in my third year of teaching writing at Ralph High School in New York, when one of my students,15-year-old Mikey,gave me a note from his mother.It explained his absence from class the day before: \"Dear Mr. McCort,Mikey's grandmother,who is eighty years of age,fell down the stairs from too much coffee and I kept Mikey at home to take care of her and his baby sister so I couldn't go to my job. Please excuse Mikey and he'll do his best in the future.P.S.His grandmother is OK.\" I had seen Mikey writing the note at his desk.I said nothing.Most parental-excuse note, I received were penned by my students.The writers of those notes didn't realize that honest excuse notes were usually dull: \"Peter was late because the alarm clock didn't go off.\" The students always said it was hard putting 20...\n\nQ: Which of the following best describes the author as a teacher?", "options": ["Honest.", "Strict.", "Hardworking.", "Wise."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1740, "question": "Names have gained increasing importance in the competitive world of higher education. As colleges struggle for market share, they are looking for names that project the image they want or reflect the changes they hope to make. Trenton State College, for example, became the College of New Jersey nine years ago when it began raising admission standards and appealing to students from throughout the state. \"All I hear in higher education is, 'Brand, brand, brand,'\" said Tim Westerbeck, who specializes in branding and is managing director of Lippmann Hearne, a marketing firm based in Chicago that works with universities and other nonprofit organizations. \"There has been a sea change over the last 10 years. Marketing used to be almost a dirty word in higher education.\" Not all efforts at name ch...\n\nQ: The case of name changing from Cal State, Hayward, to Cal State,East Bay indicates that the university   _  .", "options": ["is observed by the society", "hopes to expand its influence", "prefers to inform its teaching programs", "expects to enlarge its campus"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1927, "question": "Are you hard-working? Do you like to meet people? If your answer is \"Yes\", then we have a job for you as a waiter. Call AL Hotel at 556779! (2) SUMMER JOB Do you like to talk with people? Do you like to write stories? If you want to work for our magazine as a reporter, please call Karen at 558366. (3) HELP WANTED Do you like babies? Can you look after one baby for two days? If you are sure to take food care of it, call us at 766588. $80 or more. Today! Hurry! (4)CLEANER WANTED Can you make a large house clean and tidy? If you hope to get the job paid at $20 once, call us this evening 18:00-20:00. Tel:633800...\n\nQ: If you like children and have two days free, you can call at    _  for a job.", "options": ["766588", "633800", "556779", "558366"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1286, "question": "Not having done physical exercise for some time, I found myself a little low-spirited and couldn't study efficiently, so I decided to do some running the next day. At 6:15 the next morning, my alarm clock rang. Unwilling to rise from my bed, I turned it off and went back to sleep. However, 5 minutes later, I struggled to get up. After washing and brushing, I had my sneakers on and went out. Wow! The air was so fresh that I couldn't help breathing it deeply. I stretched my arms and legs, then started to run. I found all things around me were so attractive. Look, the branches were waving, as if they were welcoming me; the blossoming flowers were bowing, with shyness, just like girls. Listen, the wind was whispering, as if to say \"come on, girl\". What's more interesting was those two birds, p...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the writer went running with the purpose of   _  .", "options": ["seeing the beauty of nature", "making herself more active", "talking with birds", "breathing fresh air"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2693, "question": "Every day we meet people in a number of business and social situations. And the way we meet and greet them creates an impression. It's important to do so in a proper way, no matter whether you are introducing yourself to someone, or introducing two people. To keep you aware of this, we have gathered tips on how to make a proper introduction. *Always stand when making an introduction. When you are seated and someone comes up to greet you, make the effort to stand up. By doing this, you show respect for yourself and for the other person. *Always keep eye contact while making an introduction. Many people are not aware of the value of this simple action. When you make eye contact, you are giving a confident image. *Always introduce a person of lesser authority to one of greater authority. The ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, people will think you are   _   if you don't make eye contact with them.", "options": ["not honest", "not confident", "shy", "unfriendly"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1751, "question": "As winter gives way to spring, students feel like taking outdoor activities. However, do remember that accidents can happen, such as the one that happened at Taihu Lake several weeks ago. Four students from Shanghai were killed and several were injured. There were several reasons for the accident, but if the students had worn life jackets, it would have made a big difference. Therefore, it is important to take steps to avoid accidents before going on trips whether on land or water. Here are some steps: Make sure you are physically fit for any activities. You need energy for hiking or boating after a long inactive winter. Research your route . Check the weather report so you can pack the correct things so that an unexpected downpour or high winds won't destroy your day. If you are visiting ...\n\nQ: The accident at Taihu Lake is mentioned to  _  .", "options": ["warn students against traveling alone", "introduce the topic of the passage", "show the disadvantages of outdoor activities", "remind students of the importance of life jackets"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 700, "question": "After their 20-year-old son hanged himself during his winter break from the University of Arizona five years ago, Donna and Phil Satow wondered what signs they have overlooked, and started asking other students for answers. What grew from this soul searching was Ulifeline (www. Ulifeline. org), a Web site where students can get answers to questions about depression by logging on through their universities. The site has been adopted as a resource by over 120 colleges, which can customize it with local information, and over 1.3 million students have logged on with their college ID's. \"It is a very solid Web site that raises awareness of suicide, de-stigmatizes mental illness and encourages people to seek the help they need,\"said Paul Grayson, the director of counseling services at New York U...\n\nQ: Mrs. Satow would probably agree that   _", "options": ["Jed's friends can prevent her son's death", "her son's suicide is unavoidable", "Ulifeline is a worthwhile website", "depression is the final cause of suicides"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1222, "question": "Television in the United States is free. To pay for programs, there are many advertisements. Often these advertisements are short plays with actors. The following television advertisement is like many others that Americans see daily. We see a man and his wife at the breakfast table. They have been married for a long time. They are not speaking to each other. They haven't spoken to each other at the breakfast table for years. The husband is reading his newspaper. We can't see his face. The wife looks very bored as she pours a cup of coffee for him. Today, she is using a new kind of coffee for the first time. The husband picks up his cup. He isn't very interested. He tastes his coffee. Suddenly he puts down his newspaper. Something is different.! Can it be the coffee? He takes another taste....\n\nQ: The TV advertisement wants to tell the viewers   _  .      .", "options": ["to have an immediate try at the new coffee", "to have a good laugh at the good couple", "that a nice breakfast must go with nice coffee", "that advertisements can certainly increase goods production"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3289, "question": "From a very early age, some children show better self-control than others. Now, a new study that began with about 1,000 children in New Zealand has tracked how a child's low self-control can predict poor health, money troubles and even a criminal record in their adult years. Researchers have been studying this group of children for decades now. They observed the level of self-control the youngsters displayed. Parents, teachers, even the kids themselves, scored the youngsters on measures like \"acting before thinking\" and \"Persistence in reaching goals.\" The study led by Moffitt of Duke University and colleagues followed 1,000 children from birth to age 32 in Dunedin, New Zealand. \"The children who had the lowest self-control when they were age three to ten, later on had the most health prob...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["Self-control cannot be taught in schools.", "The study is restricted within few participants.", "It's never too late to deal with self-control problems.", "Good parenting can improve self-control and life success."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1932, "question": "Among professional basketball players,Jeremy Lin's background is not typical.He graduated from Harvard University,which sends few players to the NBA,and he is the only ChineseAmerican NBA player.But when you watch him on the court,there is no doubt that he belongs there.He moves with speed and grace that show years of faithful practice,which is fueled by a love for basketball. The Family Effect Lin's enjoyment of basketball actually began in Taiwan,where his father started watching it.Lin's father moved to U.S.,and his interest in the sport only grew.He passed on this love of basketball to his son,introducing him to the game at the age of five.The young Lin spent much of his youth playing basketball for fun.After each game,his parents would discuss not only his score but also his conduct t...\n\nQ: What can we learn from Jeremy Lin?", "options": ["Hard work brings success.", "We must have a father like Jeremy's.", "A good university can help us realize our dreams.", "Team honour is more important than our own success."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2950, "question": "The Streisand Effect When Barbra Streisand discovered in 2003 that a photograph of her California beach house was among 12,000 photos on the Internet as part of a collection by a photographer Kenneth Adelman, she did what any famous person would do: hit him with a $50 million lawsuit . But in trying to hold back the images, she caused a different result. Her legal actions led to almost half a million people visiting the website, viewing and copying the photos within a month. Ever since then, the effect of letting public know something you are trying to keep secret has been called the \"Streisand effect\". The problem for anyone trying to cover up information is that the Internet is the world's biggest and most useful copying machine. Put a document on to a connected machine and it will sprea...\n\nQ: What speeded up the spread of Martha's story?", "options": ["Parents' reaction.", "The authority's order.", "Martha's comment.", "Supporting from the school."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2455, "question": "Norway tops the list of countries that offers the best social policies for people over 60. Afghanistan is rated the worst. The rankings appear in the new Global Age Watch Index. Help Age International published the index of 96 countries that are home to 790-million people 60 and older. Chief Executive Officer Toby Porter said, \"For too long, older people have been excluded from international and national development planning. We have a world which is ageing fast. And what the index does is to compare and rank countries from best to worst countries in the world to grow old,\" he said. The Global Age Watch Index rates countries in four categories. \"Health, income, what we call capability - ability to carry on contributing employment. And then the final one about enabling environment - what do...\n\nQ: The purpose of The Global Age Watch Index is to  _  .", "options": ["warn governments of the severe environmental problems in their countries", "tell the difference between developing countries and developed countries[]", "get governments and people to care more about older people in the world", "urge governments to take measures to stop political and military conflicts"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 702, "question": "\"The days when the management in Western companies presented gold watches to long-serving employees to thank them for loyal service is now just a memory.\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. This new development in the shape and movement of the workforce throughout Western businesses is partly a result of the way that layers of middle management are being removed, leaving more workers responsible for their own development. \"Having workers take responsibility for their own development might be dramatic, but it is now the rule,\" says the Educational and Training Support Agency. \"Today, not only are workers more mobile, they have to run to keep up with changes.\" says the Government-founded agency.\"It is no longer enough for a worker to gain a set of skills.Workers need the abili...\n\nQ: The western workforce frequently changes their jobs partly because   _  .", "options": ["hopping from job to job has become a new trend", "employees are expecting to have more experiences in their life", "workers have to take more responsibility for themselves", "it is easy to complete themselves by doing so"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2540, "question": "It's enough to give anyone an earache. Women spend an average of about five years on the phone during their working lives, research has shown. You won't be surprised to learn that women spend 18 months longer than men on the phone -- who only chat for an average of three years. Both sexes make and receive almost the same number of calls -- 277,000 for men and 288,000 for women. But women spend 13,500 more hours in total on their conversations. More than half of those chats are work-related but people spend on average twice as long on a personal call (10 minutes ) as on a business one. Despite the explosion in mobile phone ownership, most people still prefer to use landlines, the poll found. However, when people are tired of talking, the top excuse for getting a caller off the line is to sa...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following statements is TRUE?", "options": ["Women spend about five years talking on the phone during their lifetime.", "Women make and receive the same number of calls as men do.", "On average, work-related calls are only half as long as personal calls.", "Usually a call made by a man is longer than one by a woman."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 432, "question": "Health insurance can be very expensive. Some working people do not make enough money to pay for it. In the US there is a program called Healthy Families. This program offers people health insurance at a low cost. Families are charged about $7.00 a month for every child, and $10.00 for every adult. It costs much less than any other kind of health insurance. Having health insurance is very important. With this insurance, people can see a doctor when they are sick or hurt. The program is not expensive at all, but many people are still not enrolling in it. People say that it still costs too much money. They need all of their money to pay for things like food and rent . It would be great if everyone could have health insurance. People are working hard to come up with ways to make this happen. O...\n\nQ: If a couple has two children, how much would health insurance cost every month?", "options": ["$34", "$40.", "$28.", "$24."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1028, "question": "Home to me means a sense of familiarity and nostalgia . It's fun to come home. It looks the same. It smells the same. You'll realize what's changed is you. Home is where we ran remember pain, live, and some other experiences; We parted here; My parents met here; I won three championships here. If I close my eyes, I can still have a clear picture in mind of my first home. I walk in the door and see a brown sofa surrounding a low glass-top wooden table. To the right of the living room is my first bedroom. It's empty, but it's where my earliest memories are. There is the dining room table where I celebrated birthdays, and where I cried on Halloween-when I didn't want to wear the skirt my mother made for me. I always liked standing on that table because it made me feel tall and strong. If I si...\n\nQ: What is the author's purpose of writing this passage?", "options": ["To express how much she is attached to her home.", "To declare how much she loves her first house.", "To describe the state of her family.", "To look back on her childhood."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 23, "question": "A couple who held hands at breakfast every morning even after 70 years of marriage have died 15 hours apart. Helen Felumlee, died at 92 on April 12. Her husband, 91-year-old Kenneth Felumlee, died the next morning. The couple's eight children say the two had been inseparable since meeting as teenagers, once sharing the bottom of a bunk bed on a ferry rather than sleeping on night apart. They remained deeply in love until the very end, even eating breakfast together while holding hands, said their daughter, Linda Cody. \"We knew when one went, the other was going to go,\" she said. According to Cody, about 12 hours after Helen died, Kenneth looked at his children and said, \"Mon's dead.\" He quickly began to fade, surrounded by 24 of his closest family members and friends when he died the next ...\n\nQ: From what Cody said, we can learn the children   _  .", "options": ["were not in front of their father", "don't look after their father", "foresaw their father would go", "surrounded their father"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2361, "question": "No one wants to look stupid or do the wrong thing at a new job. It is important to make the right impression from the very first day. You will face new people. You will be in a new place. It may be difficult to know what to do. Here are five tips to help you make it through the first days at a new job: 1. First impressions can last forever. Make sure you make a good one. Before your first day, find out if your new job has a dress code (rules about what you can wear to work). If so, be sure to follow it. No matter what, always be neat and clean. 2. Get to work on time. 3. Pay attention to introductions. One of the first things that your supervisor may do is to introduce you to co-workers. These co-workers will be important to you. They are the ones who will answer your questions when the bo...\n\nQ: Before you arrive at work on the first day, you should   _  .", "options": ["dress in a right way", "introduce yourself", "know your duties", "know your co-workers well"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2535, "question": "When you sleep somewhere else--like at summer camp or a friend's house--you know you're in for a fun time. It can be exciting to get away from the same old bed in the same old room in the same old house. But fun as this is, for some kids being away from home can be scary and sad. They want to go and have fun with their friends, but once they're there, they start to miss their good old bed, their good old parents, and all that everyday stuff at home. It's called being homesick. Homesick means you're upset, sad, and maybe scared. But don't feel surprised. A lot of people get homesick, even grownups. When you're used to having certain people and things around you, it can be scary when they're gone. When you're dealing with other problems, you will feel homesick, too. Some kids may feel more h...\n\nQ: One feels homesick means he's not   _  .", "options": ["upset", "sad", "scary", "full"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1919, "question": "If you're among the millions of Americans packing their vacation bags for summer trips,don't forget,however, that as soon as you step off the plane,you're expected to follow that country's laws.We took a look at one of the top countries Americans are most likely to visit and what might happen if you got caught. prefix = st1 /Mexico Smoking marijuana:If police find you smoking a cigarette which contains marijuana,they will most likely _ you overnight and you will get a fine. Carrying a firearm:You might be able to walk around with a gun in Texas,but that isn't so in Mexico,so leave your gun behind.If you wish to go hunting in Mexico.you can apply for a gun permit but expect to be charged $5,000.If you are caught bringing a firearm,Mexican policeman may take away your car and arrest you.An a...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["The laws in America are different from the ones in Mexico.", "People will be fined if they smoke marijuana.", "People will be arrested if they are caught bringing a gun.", "The police in Mexicohave right to keep the drivers' license"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2788, "question": "While the other kids seemed excited about celebrating the end-of-term party by playing games and sharing treats, Jeremy hated the very idea of the gathering. Afraid to raise the pressure too high, I decided to contribute something that was easy to purchase on the walk to school. Off we went the day of the party, approaching his school as if nothing was planned. I reminded him of our need to make a purchase, entered his favorite shop, and asked him to select the ripest bunch of grapes. He shot me an anxious look and insisted none of his classmates ever be able to notice he had something to bring to the party. My _ of a successful parenting method, resulting in delivering a sociable child to his school, diverted sharply from reality. Back on route, I did my best to hide the sinking feeling o...\n\nQ: How did the author feel when she left the shop?", "options": ["Worried.", "Satisfied.", "Grateful.", "Regretful."], "answer": 0}]